lime.com 2008-06-16

# Privacy Policy - LIME

LIME, Life Balance Media, LLC, its parent, and subsidiaries (the 'Company') is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all our users. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online through Company Web sites, which includes all of the Company sites and governs online data collection and usage by the Company. Please read the complete the Company Online Privacy Policy below and contact us if you have any questions. 

## COLLECTION AND TRACKING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced service, we request information about you. We collect personally identifiable information such as names, email addresses and demographic information such as age, gender, and zip code. We also may collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring Web site address. This information is collected both during registration on a site or in response to specific requests, for example when signing up for a newsletter, entering a sweepstakes or contest, or answering a survey. Information collected at one Company Web site will be available within the Company's family of Web sites. 

Sometimes we will give you the opportunity to opt in to offers from third parties not affiliated with the Company. If you decide to accept these offers, we will provide, with your consent, your information to the third party. However, you should note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information users consent to give to third parties not affiliated with the Company. Any information users give to another party is governed by the rules of that party's privacy policy, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. The Company is not responsible for information given to other parties. Please review their privacy policies prior to providing any information to third parties. 

## WHAT WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION

We use personal information so that we may display custom, personalized content to our visitors and send newsletters, emails, features, promotional material, surveys, and other updates to our users. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our service, respond to any problems that may arise and to gauge user trends to determine what part of our services are most popular with users. 

We may extend offers to users on behalf of our partners about a particular product or service that may be of interest to you, but we will never give out your name or personal information at any time without your permission. As result, although LIME may receive a fee from our partners for this service, LIME sends all the offers so that your personal information is never shared with any outside third party. 

We may, at times, produce reports for advertisers containing aggregate information about our users such as demographic, age, and online usage information. This allows us to work more closely with advertisers to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our users. We will never include any personal information of our users in these reports. 

We allow users of our Web site to send articles or links by email to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any email addresses (unless you are a member who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or recipient of such articles or links after they are sent. 

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation, or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation. 

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online (whether through the Company's services or any other service available online), personal or otherwise, that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you use chat, forums, bulletin boards, your email, or if you post personal information online, you may receive unsolicited messages from others. The Company has no control over this use of your personal information. 

## USE OF COOKIES

Your browser offers so-called "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a Web site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Cookies simply assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. Cookies also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our Web sites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features of our site, as well as other Web sites, will not be available to you. 

We may also place a cookie on your browser so that this and other Web Sites owned by us will recognize you as a unique, anonymous user. This will enable us to make sure that you do not see the same ad over and over, to sequence ads in a series, and to measure more accurately the number of unique visitors across our network of sites. 

Some of the banner ads displayed in our Web sites are provided by outside companies. These ads contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web sites, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. We use a reputable third party to serve some or all of the advertisements that are placed within our sites and they may use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to our sites and other sites to assist in serving advertisements to you. 

## CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

A user may, at any time, change, correct, modify, or delete any personal information they may have provided to the Company by visiting his or her User Profile. Users can also unsubscribe from any newsletters or opt out of various promotional emailings at any time by visiting his or her User Profile or clicking on "unsubscribe" links in each of our newsletters or emails. 

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Company employees are made aware of its privacy practices through periodic communications and training. We limit access to private and confidential data only to those employees with a specific need to retrieve this information and we store data on multiple service systems, in controlled, secure environments. To maintain our level of security, we conduct both internal reviews and external audits of our security measures and procedures on a regular basis. 

## CHANGES IN CORPORATE STRUCTURE

In developing our business, we might sell certain assets or the Company, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may be one of the transferred assets. 

## VISITORS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

Our Web site and the servers that make this site available worldwide are located in the United States. All matters relating to these sites are governed by the laws of the State of New York in the United States. Any information you provide will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our sites and submitting information, you authorize this transfer. 

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to maintain the highest protection for our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy or in how we will use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make changes in how we handle previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so. 

## CONTACT INFORMATION

As of April 2008 you can contact us by mail at: 

**LIME**  
c/o GAIAM  
350 Madison Avenue, 17th Floor  
New York, NY 10017  
(212) 951-3000 

_Updated Spring 2008_
